<conversations>
    <conversation ID="HDBrownie_NVM_Raven">
        <node ID="Start">
            <text>
                {{emote|*CAAW*}} =MARKOVCORVIDSENTENCE= {{emote|*CAAW*}}
            </text>
            <text Priority="1" IfIn100="2">
                {{emote|*CAAW*}} Restless in the spindle channel, phantom corvids three. {{emote|*CAAW*}}
            </text>
            <choice GotoID="End">Live and drink, nonsense bird.</choice>
        </node>
    </conversation>
    <conversation ID="HDBrownie_NVM_Raven NPC Base">
        <node ID="Start">
            <choice ID="Lenore" GotoID="Lenore">Why are you called Lenore?</choice>
        </node>
        <node ID="Lenore">
            <text>
                {{w|*The bird stares past you, as if not even hearing the question.*}}
            </text>
            <choice UseID="End" />
        </node>
    </conversation>
    <conversation ID="HDBrownie_NVM_Melancholy" Inherits="HDBrownie_NVM_Raven NPC Base">
        <node ID="Start">
            <text>
                Traveler, I shall not hear ye; circumstances make me weary,
                So begone unless you have a treatment for my heart so sore.
                Once my heart was light and floating, like a firefly emoting,
                dancing with the motes that lit the outside of my study door.
                Once I danced among the motes all floating past my study door;
                Now my spirit will not soar.
            </text>
            <text Priority="1">
                What is that you come here bearing? You who zip about wayfaring,
                Have you brought the means to heal my heart the way it was before?
                Please O Stranger, I beseech you, may my low entreaty reach you,
                Grant me that small mote of light you carry, this I ask you for!
                I'll be grateful evermore.
                <part Name="HaveItem" Blueprints="Symbiotic Firefly,Luminous Mote" AllowTemporary="true" />
            </text>
            <choice ID="End" GotoID="End">Live and drink, non-nonsense bird.</choice>
        </node>
    </conversation>
    <conversation ID="HDBrownie_NVM_Passion" Inherits="HDBrownie_NVM_Raven NPC Base">
        <node ID="Start">
            <text>
                Though you may not divine the rhyming scheme,
                There lies in hiding much more than you see here.
                Were you to simply peer past what may seem,
                'Fore long the treasure would approach and be near.
                O you errant upon the winding path,
                There holds but one last bastion in my spirit;
                I do beseech you, if as Cupid hath,
                You come across a mighty bow, please hear it:
                Do be so cordial as to let it free,
                Entrust it to my wings, so strong and agile.
                Do go, posthaste, and bring that bow to me.
            </text>
            <choice GotoID="WrongBow" IfHaveBlueprint="Short Bow,Electrobow" AllowTemporary="true">Is this the bow you wanted?</choice>
            <choice ID="End" GotoID="End">Live and drink, advanced nonsense bird.</choice>
        </node>
        <node ID="WrongBow">
            <text>
                {{w|*The bird simply gestures disappointedly.*}}
            </text>
            <choice UseID="End" />
        </node>
    </conversation>
    <conversation ID="HDBrownie_NVM_Morbidity" Inherits="HDBrownie_NVM_Raven NPC Base">
        <node ID="Start">
            <text>
                {{w|*The corvid simply stares directly through you, trembling slightly, seeing not you but only possibilities beyond you.*}}
            </text>
            <choice GotoID="Hello">Hello?</choice>
            <choice ID="End" GotoID="End">Live and drink, unsettling bird.</choice>
        </node>
        <node ID="Hello">
            <text>{{w|*There is no reply. You're not sure if the bird is even aware of your presence.}}</text>
            <choice GotoID="Poem">I was expecting a poem.</choice>
            <choice UseID="End" />
        </node>
        <node ID="Poem">
            <text>
                {{w|*The silence shatters like brittle glass.*}} Then steal it bleeding from my chest.
            </text>
            <choice GotoID="What">I'm sorry? What?</choice>
            <choice UseID="End" />
        </node>
        <node ID="What">
            <text>
                There is no poem so moving as the snuffing of a flame.
            </text>
            <choice GotoID="End">... Uh, okay. Live and drink.</choice>
        </node>
    </conversation>
</conversations>
